Guide to the Peter Gizzi Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- O·blēk Files, 1979-2005; Series III; 11.5; (18 boxes)
  - O·blēk Editions
    - Exact Change Yearbook 1995, no 1.
      - Palmer, Michael. "Exact Change Yearbook Interview", 1994 (Box 32)
      - Perril, Simon. "Treacherous Conditions of the Heart", 1994 (Box 32)
        Also includes correspondence from Mark Ford, Gonville and Caius College, Miles Champion, Lee Harwood and Anonymous (Cambridge, UK).
      - Photocopies and photostat copy of "Publisher's Note", undated (Box 32)
      - Powell, Patricia. "A Small Gathering of Bones", 1994 (Box 32)
      - Rushin, Kate. Correspondence, 1994 (Box 32)
      - Stationery and Publishing letter, 1993 (Box 32)
      - Tietz, Ward. Children's book, 1994 (Box 32)
      - Various material, circa 1994; 5 (Box 32)
        Includes correspondence or manuscripts from Reality Studios (Ken Edwards), Denise Riley, Iliassa Sequin, Kelvin Corcoran, Anthony Mellors, Maurice Scully, Catherine Walsh, G.F. Dutton, Ulli Freer, Dr. D.S. Marriott, John Ashbery, Jeff Derksen, Christine Stewart, Susan Clark, Pasquale Verdicchio, Lyn Hejinian, Julie Kalendek, University of Massachusetts, Jeff Twitchell, and others.
      - Waldrop, Rosmarie, undated; 2 (Box 32)
      - Yearbook, publisher's introduction, undated (Box 32)
    - Hocquard, Emmanuel. Theory of Tables (1994), 1993-1994; 9 (Box 33)
    - Rehm, Pam. Piecework (1992), 1991-1992; 3 (Box 33)
    - Sequin, Iliassa. Quintets (1991), 1990-1991; 2 (Box 33)
    - Coolidge, Clark and Philip Guston. Baffling Means: Writings / Drawings (1991), 1990-1991; 3 (Box 33)
    - Willis, Elizabeth. A/O (1991), 1990-1991; 3 (Box 33)
    - McGrath, Connell. With Words (1991), circa 1991; 3 (Box 33)
      Also includes proofs of "Light Still Enough to Witness" by Terrel Hale and proofs of "Quintets" by Iliassa Sequin.
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1998
      - B.City: Special Sestina Issue, 1993 (Box 33)
        Also includes McNaughton and Gunn, Inc. correspondence.
      - Financial correspondence and records, 1996-1998; 3 (Box 33)
      - O·blēk advertisement proof, undated (Box 33)
      - "O·blēk editions / $", 1992 (Box 33)
      - "O·blēk / Prov. / Buffalo", 1993 (Box 33)
- Writings by Others, 1990-2007; Series IV; 5.21; (6 boxes)
  Arranged alphabetically by author or title.
  Series IV. consists of typescripts of writings by others submitted to Peter Gizzi for his comment.
  - Ali, Kazim. "The Fortieth Day", undated (Box 33)
  - "AWP Austin 2006 name tag" (Box 33)
  - Baus, Eric. "A Ding and Its Echo (I Left Him With The Wolves)", 2004-2005 (Box 33)
  - Baus, Eric. "Something Else the Title Was", undated (Box 33)
  - Baus, Eric. "The To Sound", 2003 (Box 33)
  - Bang, Mary Jo. "Elegy", 2006 (Box 33)
  - Bernstein, Charles. "Girly Man", 2006 (Box 33)
  - Bianchi, Raymond L. "A Clot of Screams", undated (Box 34)
  - Blaser, Robin. "The Collected Essays", 2004; 5 (Box 34)
  - Blaser, Robin. "The Holy Forest, Collected Poems of Robin Blaser", undated (Box 34)
  - Bolton, Joshua. Poems, undated (Box 34)
  - Brathwaite, Kamau. "Salt", 2003 (Box 34)
  - Brinks, Dave. "If Ever There Were One", undated (Box 34)
    Also includes "German By the Grace of Goethe" by Marjorie Perloff and "Nude Siren" by Peter Richards.
  - Brinks, Dave. "Poems From The Secret Brain", undated (Box 34)
    Also includes poems by Kristina Martino and "Halcyon Days - Amidst Our Arms As Quiet You Shall Be".
  - Buck, Marie. "FutureSex / LoveSounds", undated (Box 34)
  - Buck, Marie. Poems, undated (Box 34)
  - Burdette, Nicole. "Men", 2004 (Box 34)
  - Burdette, Nicole. "The Telling", undated (Box 34)
    Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services: Disk 7, "The Telling" (2006)
  - Caples, Garrett. "A Consumer Guide To Charles Bernstein", undated (Box 34)
    Also includes "John Ashbery and You."
  - Carrier, Chris S. "After Dayton", 2007 (Box 34)
  - "Caveats and Apologies" (Box 34)
  - Choffel, Julie. "Independent Study: History of the Cyric", 2003 (Box 34)
  - "Close To The Art of Those Fearless At Sea", undated (Box 34)
  - Clover, Joshua. Promotion material, 2006 (Box 35)
  - Clune, Michael. Poems, 2004 (Box 35)
  - Cohen, Alicia Avalee. "Seeing Seeing", 2002 (Box 35)
  - Coolidge, Clark. "Book of Stirs: Ex Libris Prospero", 1993 (Box 35)
  - Coolidge, Clark. "In Dream", 1991 (Box 35)
  - Coolidge, Clark. "Man With His Head Out (The Van Gogh Entries)", 1991 (Box 35)
  - Coolidge, Clark. "My Godard, A Departure", 2003 (Box 35)
  - Coolidge, Clark. "Odes of Roba", 1990 (Box 35)
  - Coultas, Brenda. "The Marvelous Bones of Time", undated (Box 35)
  - "Court Green 2", undated (Box 35)
  - Creeley, Robert. "If I Were Writing This", undated (Box 35)
  - Creeley, Robert. "Selected Poems", 2005; 2 (Box 35)
  - Cross, Michael. "Involuntary Vision", undated (Box 35)
    Also includes "Egypt Judaea" by Edwin Frank.
  - Cunningham, Brent. "Bird and Forest", 2005 (Box 35)
  - Deming, Richard. "Environed By The Self", 2005 (Box 35)
  - Di, Xue. "Another Kind of Tenderness", 2004 (Box 35)
  - Di Leo, Jefferey R. "A Whore's Answer To A Whore: The Prostitution of Jack Spicer", 2006 (Box 35)
  - Donohoe, Catherine. "Crude Renderings", 2007 (Box 35)
  - Donohoe, Katie. Poems, undated (Box 35)
  - "Englished By Diverse Hands", undated (Box 35)
  - Fambrough, Monica. "Thesis", undated (Box 35)
  - Finkelstein, Norman. "Late Duncan: From Poetry To Scripture", undated (Box 35)
  - Finkelstein, Norman. "The Sacred and The Real in the Tablets of Armand Schwerner", undated (Box 35)
  - Fisher, Dan. "Fugue Report", 2004 (Box 35)
  - Flis, Brad. "Peasants", undated (Box 35)
    Also includes "The First Chapter" by Sean Casey and "Narrative Occupation and Uneven Enclosure" by Taylor Brady.
  - Friedman, Michael. "Martian Dawn", undated (Box 36)
  - Gilbert, Alan. "Looking Ahead To The Present", 2002 (Box 36)
  - "Gizzi Class", 2004 (Box 36)
  - Goodan, Kevin. "In The Ghost - House Acquainted", 2004 (Box 36)
  - Gordon, Noah Eli. "The Frequencies", undated (Box 36)
  - Gordon, Noah Eli. "Notes Toward The Spectacle", undated (Box 36)
  - Guest, Barbara. "Collected Poems", 2007 (Box 36)
  - Guest, Barbara. Partisan Review photocopy, undated (Box 36)
    Also includes copies of Barbara Guest's earliest published poems.
  - "Handmade Booklets", undated (Box 36)
    Includes "Every Other Week Is Also A Medium" by Sean Hansen and "Larry Brown / Robert Creeley".
  - Hawkey, Christian. "The Book of Funnels", undated (Box 36)
  - Hawley, Anthony. "Paradise Gelatin", undated (Box 36)
  - Henry, Brian. "Broken Tooth", undated (Box 36)
  - Holt, Kelly. "Dissertation Prospectus", 2005 (Box 36)
    Also includes "Recognize Me" by Juliana Leslie.
  - Holt, Kelly. "Medieval Influences On The Berkeley Renaissance", 2004 (Box 36)
  - Holt, Kelly. "Spicer's Poetic Correspondence: A Pun The Letter Reflects", undated (Box 36)
  - Howe, Fanny. "Selected Essays", undated (Box 36)
  - Howe, Fanny. "The Wedding Dress", 2002 (Box 36)
  - Iijima, Brenda. "If Not Metamorphic", undated (Box 36)
  - "James Laughlin Award folder, with list", 2007 (Box 36)
  - Jovanelli, Megan London. "Truth Letteres", 2000 (Box 36)
  - Kaplan. "Redefining Ekphrasis" (Box 36)
  - Kelleher, Michael. "Human Scale", 2007 (Box 36)
  - Kuhl, Nancy. Resumé, undated (Box 36)
  - Kuhl, Nancy. "The Wife Of The Left Hand", undated (Box 36)
  - Kunin, Aaron. "Address To The Machine World", 2003 (Box 36)
    Also includes "Tiger, Tiger" by Noah Eli Gordon.
  - Lacour, Justin B. "In The Country Of My Radio", 2004 (Box 36)
  - Lasky, Dorothea. "Thesis Intro and Poems", 2003 (Box 36)
  - Lerger. "Angle of Yaw", undated (Box 36)
  - Leslie, Juliana. "Air & Space Museum", undated; 3 (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Lesle. "Landscapes I and II", 2005-2006; 2 (Box 37)
  - Loren, Jesse. "The Fleshing Words", 2005 (Box 37)
  - Loren, Jesse. "War and Words in Cotemporary Poetry" (Box 37)
  - Los Angeles Book Review, 2003 February (Box 37)
    Includes a transcript of "The Dice Players", "From Promise X: A Memoir" by Lisa Jarnot, and "Casida Of The Reclining Woman".
  - Machlin, Dan. "Dear Body", 2007 (Box 37)
  - "Matadora", undated (Box 37)
  - Mathys, Ted. "Forge" (Box 37)
  - Matthews, Sharon. Poems, 2005 (Box 37)
    Also includes "Creation" by Nicole Burdette and "Everything Preserved: Poems 1955-2005" by Landis Everson.
  - Mayer, Bernadette. "Story and More Stories", 2006 (Box 37)
  - McCarron, Andrew and Justin Jamail. "The Absolute of Feelings", 2005 (Box 37)
    Also includes "Ship Shape" by Monica Fambrough.
  - McMorris, Mark. "Blaze of the Poui", undated (Box 37)
  - Meetze, James. "Come On Die Young", undated (Box 37)
  - Meetze, James. "I Have Designed This For You", undated (Box 37)
  - Mendoza, Mark. "Thought's Scores: A-tuning and Orchestrations on Zukofsky's 'A'", undated (Box 37)
  - Mohammad, Kasey Silem. Recommendation, 2006 (Box 37)
  - Morgan, Andrew. "Can't The Ritualist Uncork His Fingers For A Moment", 2006 (Box 37)
  - Morrison, Rusty. "The Truth Keeps Calm Biding Its Story", 2007 (Box 37)
  - Moudry, Nick. "Decoy", 2004 (Box 37)
  - Naropa University Summer Writing Program, 2006 (Box 37)
  - Nichols, Travis. "The Empirical Field", undated (Box 37)
  - Northrop, Kate. "Things Are Disappearing Here", undated (Box 37)
  - Notley, Alice. "The Collected Poems of Ted Berrigan", undated (Box 37)
  - O'Brien, Geoffrey. Stories, 2006 (Box 37)
  - Olson, Charles. "I Set Out Now In A Box Upon The Sea", undated (Box 37)
  - Oppen, George. "Selected Prose, Daybooks and Papers", 2007; 2 (Box 37)
  - Palattella, John. "No Other Country", undated (Box 37)
    Also includes "Poetry and Commitment: Plenary Lecture, Conference on Poetry and Politics, University of Stirling, Scotland, July 13, 2006."
  - Perloff, Marjorie, 2005 (Box 37)
  - "Pink Is The New Black", undated (Box 37)
  - "Relative Heat Index", undated (Box 37)
    Also includes "Seductive Vienna" by Marjorie Perloff.
  - Polito, Robert. "Bits Of Me Scattered Everywhere: Ray Davies and The Kinks", 2002 (Box 38)
    Also includes "Edgar G. Ulmer: Three Days Of Screenings and Talks".
  - Prevallet, Kristin. "The Parasite Poems", 2003 (Box 38)
  - Rich, Adrienne. "Wall Paper", 2005 (Box 38)
  - Ruggieri, Jennifer. "Transition Objects," thesis, 2007 (Box 38)
  - Scharf, Michael. "Ready Contents In The New Language...", undated (Box 38)
    Also includes "Kent Jones - 8/2003" and Steven Zultawski's "To Hell With It".
  - Scharf, Michael. "Telemachiad", 1999 (Box 38)
  - Scharf, Michael. "Vérité", 2002 (Box 38)
  - Smirou, Sébastien. "My Laurent I - The Battles", undated (Box 38)
    Also includes "The Gothic Guest" by Andrew Joron, "Barbara Guest, 1920-2006: In Memoriam", and old poems by [Marie B.].
  - Sharma, Prageeta. "The Opening Question", undated (Box 38)
  - Shaughnessy, Brenda. "Human Dark With Sugar", undated (Box 38)
  - Shea, James. "Dream Trail", undated (Box 38)
  - Smith, Rod. "The Good House and Other Poems", 2007 (Box 38)
  - Smith, Rod. "Music Or Honesty", undated (Box 38)
  - Solomon, Laura. "Blue And Red Things", undated (Box 38)
    Also includes "Juliana Spahr: The Crisis of Lanugage In Twentieth Century Literature".
  - Solomon, Laura. "Poems", undated (Box 38)
  - Stevens, Wallace. "The Wallace Stevens Journal, volume 28, number 2", photocopies, 2004 (Box 38)
  - Stevens, Wallace. Panel, 2006 (Box 38)
  - Stockman, Soren. "Poems", 2006 (Box 38)
  - Stroffolino, Chris. "Speculative Primitive", 2004 (Box 38)
  - Tamminen, Suzanna. Wesleyan University, 2005 (Box 38)
  - Todd, Glenn. "The Ballad of Lemon and Crow", undated (Box 38)
  - Truitt, Sam. Resume and writings, 2002 (Box 38)
    Also includes "Vertical Elegies 5: The Section", "Falltime" and "Raton Rex".
  - Various writings, 2004-2006; 6 (Box 38)
    Copies of electronic files available through Access Services: Disk 8, "K. Waldrop Book Rev."
    Includes "Knowledge Blobs" by Aaron Kunin, "In Praise Of Love" by Jean-Luc Godard, "Homo-Safari" by Rebecca Cole Heinowitz, Ars Poetica 2006 Poster and Pamphlet, Cue Art Foundation correspondence, "American Dream" by Lori Shine, "Spicer's Reason To Be-Leave" by Norman Finkelstein, poems by L. Olstein, "The Called-Back Wreck of Things" by Sara Veglahn, "Steady Now, Mr. Sitwell" by Nicole Burdette and Steve Clark, "The Letters of James Schuyler to Frank O'Hara", "Shelley In The Navy-Colored Chair" by Barbara Guest, "Dialect" by Sianne Ngai and other materials and writings.
  - Various writings, undated; 2 (Box 39)
    Includes "Air and Such: An Essay on Biotherm", "Kerouac, Berrigan and The Poetics of Providence" by Marisa Januzzi, "Poetic Obligations" by Michael Palmer, "Bazin At Work", "Don't Ever Get Famous" edited by Daniel Kane, "F.Y.I.: Correspondence and The Mutation of Frank O'Hara's Personism", "Knights of Cups", "Confidential Publication Proposal For 'Grave of Light'" by Alice Notley, poems by Stephen Lindow, Robert Creeley memorial material, and Michael Friedman material.
  - Various poems, undated (Box 39)
    Includes poems by Justin Lacour, Dara Wier, Kerry O'Keefe, Lori Shine and Britton Shurley.
  - Veglahn, Sara. "The Called-Back Wreck Of Things", undated (Box 39)
  - Waldrop, Keith. Translation of Charles Baudelaire's "The Flowers of Evil", 2005 (Box 39)
  - Waldrop, Keith. "Fu Manchu", 2005 (Box 40)
    Copies of electronic files available through Access Services: Disk 9, "For Peter - Keith"
  - Waldrop, Keith. "Samples {-Stray Translations-}", undated; 2 (Box 40)
  - Wolff, Rebecca. "Poems," with resume, 2005 (Box 40)
  - Zultanski, Steven. "A View From Form", undated (Box 40)
    Also includes "Mr. Dynamite Splits" by Thomas Sayers Ellis.
  - Zurawski, Magdalena. "Personal Statement", 2006 (Box 40)
- Other Papers, 1960-2006; Series V; 1.37; (8 boxes)
  Organized into two subseries: Personal Papers and Professional Papers.
  Series V. consists of other papers relating to various aspects of Gizzi's personal and professional life.
  - Personal Papers
    - Audio recordings, undated; 3 audiocassettes (Box 40)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Box 40 (audio cassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "B. University MFA Reading 06? 07? student artist response for ready and talk", 2006 (Box 40)
    - Chinese Incense Burner, undated (Box 41)
    - Diplomas: New Hampton School and Brown University, 1978, 1991 (Box 41)
    - "Early miscellaneous from my Mom" (Box 41)
      Includes U.S. Passport (1990), a copy of birth certificate, Anthony Gizzi's (father) pay record from U.S. Army, Mothers' Day card made by Peter Gizzi as a child, various photographs and a Christmas card made by Peter Gizzi for his parents.
    - Photographs, stickers and postcard, circa 1960-1990s (Box 41)
    - NY School Encyclopedia, undated (Box 41)
    - Marine Band Harmonica, 1969 (Box 41)
    - Seraphin Gallery business card, undated (Box 42)
    - Sisselman, Brian. 61 color slides, 1980 (Box 42)
    - Student identification cards and passport, 1983-2001 (Box 42)
  - Professional Papers
    - France, 1998-1999 (Box 29)
    - Selected poems - Maps, Mirrors, Things, circa 1999 (Box 29)
    - Drafts, Journals, projects - never realized, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Word Up (Box 29)
    - Notes and Materials - Tarot Poems, 1998 (Box 29)
    - Truitt, Sam. Interview, The Voice, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Waldrop, Keith. Interview, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
    - McGrath, Connell. O·blēk, 1991 (Box 29)
    - First Festival of Literary Magazines, 2002 (Box 29)
    - NYC Bibliography, 1995-1999 (Box 29)
    - Artificial Heart, cover proofs, 1998 (Box 29)
    - Western themed photographic prints of Peter Gizzi, undated; 4 (Box 29)
    - Posters - Poetry reading in honor of Richard Wlibur, 2005 (Box 29)
    - "Philly Talk with Steve Farmer", 1998-1999 (Box 29)
    - "Mail and other stuff, Santa Cruz", 1995-1998 (Box 29)
    - Brown - Buffalo, 1991-1994 (Box 29)
    - "Professional memberships", 1998 (Box 29)
    - Journals (Anthology letters), 1994-2003; 2 (Box 29)
    - Translation of Cliche, undated (Box 30)
    - Valéry / Hocquard, translation, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Translations - Claude and Anne Marie Piece, undated (Box 30)
    - "Reading Letters - North America, Europe, Rejections", undated (Box 30)
    - Book Letters, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Film Criticism, 2002 (Box 30)
    - Addresses, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - Posters and Broadsides, 1990-2004 (Box 44 (Oversize))
      Includes a poster for the New Orleans School for the Imagination's "Festival For The Imagination" (2004), a poster for "Poesie Americaina de Aujourd'hui Dijon Accueille", a poster for a Robin Blaser poetry review, and a French poster for O·blēk (1990).
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-2006 (Box 44 (Oversize))
      Includes: a letter from Rosmaire Waldrop to Peter Gizzi (2004), Archi Rand correspondence and 35mm slides, a laminated copy of Jess Collins' 1991 cover for O·blēk, Ledger Domain artwork (circa 1995), a selection of poems sent to Howard Grant (1998), a copy of Revival with a "Byrne" photo, a poster for the First Annual St. George Poetry Festival (2001), handouts for the Summer Literary Seminars in Russia (2006), a Barbara Guest memorial poster (2006), a letter and group photos from Cary [Blake?] (2005), Peter Gizzi's SUNY: Buffalo PhD certificate and student transcript, four photographs of Peter Gizzi by Robert Seydel (1977), and mechanicals for Periplum (1992).
    - K. Waldrop, Claude Royet Journoud, Roger le Port, photographic portrait with overlayed paint, 1989 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Margaret Maynard (Cimini) portrait of Peter Gizzi, 1986 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Peter Gizzi self portrait as Odysseus as Telemachus (during Pound days), 1980 (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Electronic Files, 1990s-2009; Series VI; 0.83; (2 boxes) + circa 2 gigabytes
  Email files: Access is restricted during the lifetime of Peter Gizzi. Files in the "Restricted files" folder: restricted until 2020 January 1.
  Copies of other electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Organized into three subseries: Macbook Files, IMac Files, and Computer Disks.
  The digital component of the Peter Gizzi papers consists of files from two computers, loose disks, and email archives. Files and email were copied off two working computers at Gizzi's residence in Holyoke, MA, on 2009 October 7. The word processing files include drafts of writings, research notes, correspondence, professional documents, and teaching and lecture notes.
  - Macbook files, 2008-2009
    This subseries includes folders and files from a Macbook 3.1.
    The hard drive on this machine crashed and was restored by an unidentified commercial vendor prior to its acquisition by the library. Most records on the Macbook are dated 2008 March 10 (recovery date). Files created following the hard drive recovery have later dates.
    - Works, 2008-2009
      - Collected Poems
      - Selected Prose
      - Selected Poems 05
      - Uncollected Poems
      - Artificial Heart
      - My CIPM Book
      - Olivier Brossard essays on PG
      - Outernationale Etc.
      - Periplum and Other Poems
      - R E V I V A L
      - SVOLAW Wesleyan Final MS
      - Older Files
    - Editing Misc, 2008-2009
      - conjunct film issue
      - Real Shadows
      - Seydel cat
    - Misc Notes Talks, 2008-2009
      - AWP Talk Revision
      - Creeley obit
      - DC Talk
      - Fargue intro
      - Film Crit
      - One Big Self Review
      - stevens panel
      - structure & surprise
      - USC film thing
    - Other Poem Misc, 2008-2009
      - AFI Title Poems
      - Fence Anthology
      - lyricpostmodernisms
      - MacDowell Fall 05
      - Norton Hybrid
      - poems out or going out
      - poems sent as attachments
      - poems, notes, 06
      - Reginald's Anthology
      - wes anthology
    - Professional, 2008-2009
      - Gizzi Headshot
      - Grant Stuff
      - 06 awp stuff
      - Bios
      - blurbs
      - CD Nomination
      - Contemp Authors
      - Creeley Letters
      - Naropa 2007
      - NYS Entires for PG
      - Readers Reports
      - slovakia stuff
      - SLS 06 Russia
      - U of Oregon profile
      - Vita
    - Downloads Poetry, 2008-2009
      - andy morgan
      - auggie downloads
      - Axel Avakar
      - BBR.proofs.Gizzi
      - Bob Downloads
      - Brinks book
      - chicago poetry anthology
      - creely poems 05
      - edwin
      - Eric G. poems
      - friedlander piece
      - fulcrum pdf's 05
      - John Palatella stuff
      - jon hassel
      - Landis - poems...onjunctions
      - Nicole's book
      - noah reviews
      - Perloff=Friedlander_report+
      - Phillipe Beck
      - Povincetown
      - Sosnowski
      - tomsayersellis
      - Vancouver Conference 63
      - watts
    - Jaffe etc., 2008-2009
    - Teaching Notes & Lectures, 2008-2009
      - Another Tradition
      - NY School Class
      - Workshop Files
    - Waldrop Interview, 2008-2009
    - Restricted email files
      Restricted during the lifetime of Peter Gizzi.
  - IMac files, 2009
    This subseries includes folders and files from an iMac. Copied files were given the transfer date of 2009-10-07.
    - Grant Stuff, 2009 October 7
    - Book Reviews, 2009 October 7
    - Introductions, 2009 October 7
    - OBlek Editions Chapbooks, 2009 October 7
    - Poetry, 2009 October 7
    - Restricted files, 2009 October 7
      Restricted until January 1, 2020.
    - Translations, 2009 October 7
    - Vita, 2009 October 7
    - Waldrop Interview 98, 2009 October 7
  - Computer disks, 1990s-2000s; 2 mini discs, 5 CD-R, 1 5.25-inch floppy disk, and 40 3.5-inch floppy disks
    Boxes 48-49 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.